Chapter 1: After the Fierce Battle

In the Paladia Kingdom, at a hilly area near a farming village thirty kilometers west of the capital...

The entire area was completely destroyed. The ground was gouged open, with slabs of soil turned up everywhere. But contrary to the disastrous sight, a fantastical spectacle was taking place in the surroundings. Water hung in the air as mist, creating a rainbow. Rio walked beneath such a sky with Lucius’s corpse burning brightly behind him. He walked until he reached Christina in her tattered dress and the feverish Flora who had fallen unconscious.

“Is Princess Flora okay?” Rio asked Christina as he sheathed his sword at his waist. Christina had been staring at the mystical sight of Rio passing under the rainbow in a daze, but snapped back to her senses to explain Flora’s symptoms.

“Oh... Umm, she was bitten by a venomous spider in the forest and has a fever.”

“A venomous spider... Have you tried casting Purgo?”

“Y-Yes. But it isn’t a poison that can be treated with magic...” Christina regained her composure a little and examined Flora’s state with a pale face.

“I see...” Rio looked down at Flora’s fever-flushed face.

Detoxification magic can only decompose harmful substances inside the body into harmless substances, which means her body is being attacked by an infection rather than a toxic substance. She may heal if I strengthen her natural recovery with spirit arts, but...

There was another recovery method that would have a more immediate and reliable effect. And so, Rio decided to use that instead. He reached into the pocket of his coat and moved his mouth faintly to chant a spell.

“Dissolvo.”

The space beneath his coat immediately distorted and a small bottle appeared in his hand. Rio grabbed it and took his hand out of his pocket. To Christina and the other figure standing nearby, it looked like Rio had taken it out of his pocket normally.

“Take this. It’s a powerful magic potion that can be considered a panacea. She looks fairly exhausted so it may take some time before she regains her stamina, but it should treat the poison right away,” Rio said, holding the bottle out to Christina. It contained a secret recipe made by the spirit folk, so its effect was guaranteed.

“Are you sure...?” Christina blinked in hesitation.

“Of course?” Rio cocked his head, unsure of why she was asking such a thing.

“Th-Thank you so much,” Christina said with her sincerest gratitude and accepted the bottle.

“It’s fine. More importantly, your injuries...” Rio asked, looking at Christina’s appearance.

Her bare, dainty feet were peeking out from under the tattered hem of her muddy dress. They were clearly stained with blood, making it obvious that she was injured. There was a magic-sealing collar around her delicate neck, adding to the tragic sight.

“I-I’m fine. I was walking through the forest barefoot, but it isn’t anything major.” Christina moved her hands to cover her dirty feet in a fluster.

Rio reached inside his coat pocket once more and whispered the discharge spell to retrieve another bottle. He then offered it to Christina. “Pour this over the wound and drink the rest. It’ll ease any pain you have in your body. I’ll remove that collar later.”

“Umm, magic potions are meant to be fairly valuable items... Please use it on your own wounds before me,” Christina said hesitantly, looking at Rio’s bloodstained coat.

However, to Rio, it was something he could mass-produce, and he had no qualms about using it. “I applied some minimal treatment to my wounds while I was fighting, so I’m fine. The more pressing matter right now is the person approaching from over there, so I’m going to deal with that while you treat Princess Flora.”

Rio half-forced the bottle into her hands before turning his gaze to the approaching third party—the Paladia Kingdom’s first prince, Duran. His gaze wasn’t entirely hostile, but Rio placed a hand on his sword handle warily. However, Duran held both his hands up as he approached, expressing his lack of intention to fight.

“Stop. I do not wish to fight you.”

“But you were Lucius’s ally, no?” Rio asked.

Duran was the one who had told Rio of Lucius’s location while he was in the capital. He had even accompanied Lucius here to spectate the battle; there was plenty enough reason to conclude that the two of them were allies.

“We were comrades in arms who had fought on the same battlefield before, but I’m a prince and he was a mercenary. We were bound by no more than a contract in the end. There’s no way I would consider retaliating just because he was killed—all the less after seeing you fight just now. I’m not that reckless of a fool.” Duran recalled the sight of Lucius fighting Rio and laughed with a hint of exasperation.

“Why were you here with Lucius, then?”

“He asked me to lure you here, but after meeting you in the capital, you piqued my interest. That’s why I wanted to watch your battle with him—I’m no more than a curious onlooker, really. Ah, but I did agree to accept one of the royal sisters as a reward for my assistance,” Duran answered honestly, turning his gaze to Christina, who was feeding Flora the medicine.

Rio’s gaze grew sharper. “So you want the two of them?”

“There’s no way you would allow that, no? As I said, I do not wish to oppose you.” Duran’s attitude remained as carefree as ever.

“In that case, would I be right to assume you have no problem with me taking the two of them away from here?” Rio asked, searching Duran’s expression.

“Sure, I don’t care,” Duran replied, nodding readily. “But I’d like to negotiate with you a little first.”

“...About what?” Rio asked with suspicion. Duran’s connection to Lucius alone was enough to make Rio cautious, so those words immediately made him suspect an ulterior motive.

“Don’t be so wary. Like I said just now, I don’t need those two. Instead—what was your name again? Rio, or Haruto?”

“Rio is a name I have discarded. Please call me Haruto,” Rio answered with a glance at Christina and Flora.

“I see. Then, Haruto. Would you have any interest in working for Paladia...? In working for me? I want you more than those two,” Duran said, suddenly making an unexpected proposal.

“...Huh?” Rio made a bewildered face at the topic at hand, which surpassed his expectations.

Duran began his headhunting pitch with an entirely serious expression. “I’m asking that you work for me. I can give you whatever you want, be it money, power, or women.”

“No, I will not,” Rio declined clearly despite his bewilderment.

“Give it some careful thought before you give an answer. You may be wondering what I’m going on about so suddenly, but I’m being completely serious. I’m not trying to trap you into anything. I also don’t have an ulterior motive,” Duran appealed persistently.

“Even if you say that... What made you bring this up?”

Just what is his goal?

“A most reasonable point. How about we discuss this more at the castle over some alcohol and a seat?” Duran nodded solemnly, coming closer to Rio.

“I humbly pass on that offer.”

The Paladia Castle was where Duran had the greatest amount of power. There was no reason for Rio to go out of his way to visit such a place.

“Come on now, don’t be like that.” Duran was extremely persistent.

Rio stepped back from him. “N-No thank you. I’ll listen to whatever you want to say here.”

“Hmph... What a killjoy. But I guess there’s nothing I can do—I don’t want to overstep my boundaries and antagonize you.” Duran sighed dramatically and accepted Rio’s words with reluctance. With that, Rio could see Duran really didn’t have any ill will.

He really throws me for a loop... Rio’s guard relaxed for the first time.

He lowered the hand he had over his sword and sighed.

“Let’s get back on topic, then. Do you have an interest in working for me?” Duran said, encouraging Rio with an eager look.

“Honestly, the fact you got along with Lucius as comrades in arms is enough reason for me to decline.” There were myriad other reasons he couldn’t explain well enough, so Rio chose to answer that way.

“Hmm. So you consider me to be the same as Lucius?”

He already knew he would never work for him, so Rio spoke his thoughts without bothering to hide the truth. “Not exactly—but I cannot trust you.”

“Ha ha ha! I see you really hated that man a lot. Well, that’s only understandable after he killed your mother... But if he was walking the road of heresy, then I’m walking the road of domination. Power is justice—I take whatever I want with my own hands. I suppose I’m similar to Lucius in that way, and I won’t deny I have the temperament of a tyrant, but my tastes aren’t as terrible as his. Thus, I’m not the same as him, but we were similar enough for me to find some parts of him tolerable.”

Duran showed no offense at being compared to Lucius and instead started rambling fluently about himself. He even grinned when he called himself a tyrant. It was probably his way of making himself sound appealing to Rio as an employer.

“...You speak very frankly.”

If Duran really is trying to scout me, he should have phrased his words a little more nicely, Rio thought.

“That’s because I’m seriously trying to employ you. If I lied to you now, what would I do once you’re actually hired?” Duran answered openly.

“A just reason. But even then, I still question your decision to hire a stranger who just killed your acquaintance,” Rio argued back.

“We’re not complete strangers, and one needs to be open-minded to walk the road of dominance. Whether you killed a friend of mine or not, I want what I want. That’s why I’ll say it one more time—I want you more than the two princesses. Will you work for me?” Duran tried to persuade Rio once more.

“We’re going around in circles,” Rio said with a wry smile and a shrug.

Duran chuckled. “Well, we’d be done right away if you’d just agree.”

“I’m flattered by the offer, but why do you have such a high opinion of me?” Rio sighed at Duran’s tenacity.

“Bwa ha ha! Why, it’s simple—I love strong people. I want them for myself. That’s why I want you. By any means possible.”

“Why are you so desperate for strong people? Is it for the dominance that Your Highness spoke of earlier?”

Dominance—the power to subdue others and make them obey. The fact they were talking like this meant Rio was being dragged into Duran’s pacing already, but Rio decided to ask anyway.

“It’s my ideal way of being, but it’s not completely related. In short, I believe in the need to look at things more broadly.”

“By which you mean...?”

“My kingdom is merely one of many small kingdoms. That’s why the kingdom needs enough power not to be looked down upon by other kingdoms in a diplomatic sense. I pride myself in being able to do the work of a thousand foot soldiers, but there are skilled warriors in other kingdoms, and we’re no match for the resources of a major nation. That’s why we’ve formed an alliance with the Proxia Empire, but we’re still a small kingdom in their eyes. I cannot stand for my kingdom being seen as the weak to be eaten. For the future of the kingdom, I need to overturn that view. Do you understand?” Duran looked at Rio with fire burning in his gaze.

“You need military power so that other kingdoms won’t look down on you?”

“That’s right,” Duran nodded smugly. “There are countless small kingdoms crowded around us, and they’re constantly in a restless state. I personally don’t want to pick fights with nothing to gain, but war could start at any moment depending on the major nations backing them. Thus, I’m constantly in search of strong people.”

“When it comes to conflict, there are times when words cannot solve everything. I agree that strength is required in such cases.”

However, the way Duran phrased his words made it sound like he was willing to start war when there was something to gain. Rio couldn’t agree with a stance like that.

“A nonaggressive defense approach. The act of proactively avoiding conflict as long as the other party doesn’t make a move, huh? But there’s a countless number of small kingdoms around us, so we cannot exist without interacting with them. Once you consider the scheming of powerful nations on top of that, there’s no way we can use naive methods of nonaggressive defense. In order to feed the people, we have to pursue the profits of the kingdom before anything else.”

“I’m sure you do. However...I do not wish to be associated with any particular kingdom,” Rio uttered tiredly, truthfully.

Duran laughed heartily. “Hah! You have that much strength, yet you don’t want to be associated with a kingdom. Here I was thinking you were pursuing the path of justice, when you actually seek detachment from the real world. Do you intend on becoming a hermit?”

“Who knows? Perhaps I may,” Rio chuckled lightly, dodging the question.

“Hmm... Has the demon haunting you been exorcised now that you’ve exacted your revenge? You have no spirit. Overly ambitious subordinates are a problem, but completely apathetic ones are troublesome as well. They’re terribly difficult to motivate.” Contrary to his words, Duran stifled his hearty laughter as he spoke.

“In that case, please give up on recruiting me.”

“Mm... No. I won’t back down that easily. I can see you have enough strength hidden to overthrow a battlefield. No, an entire kingdom.”

“I’m technically an honorary knight of the Galarc Kingdom...”

Will you continue your recruiting attempt in spite of that? The Paladia Kingdom is on the side of the Proxia Empire, hostile to the Galarc Kingdom, no? Rio implied.

“I am aware. That’s why I can’t leave you as is. As long as Paladia is part of the Proxian side of things, I fear we could face you on the battlefield one day.”

“In that case, you can be at ease. I do not intend on standing on the battlefield.”

He hadn’t wanted a title in the first place, which was why he was made an honorary knight. He had no obligations to the kingdom, but all the benefits—it was a special case.

“Even if you have no intention yourself, the state of affairs may not permit such a thing. You might also change your mind. For example, if someone close to you is taken hostage. Considering how you walked the path of revenge, it’s a perfectly realistic possibility, no? You may seem like a coldhearted person at times, but you’re not heartless. Those two princesses there weren’t close to you, yet you protected them to the end perfectly,” Duran said, looking at Christina and Flora behind Rio.

Flora was still lying limply, but Christina had finished feeding her the medicine. She’d also finished her own bottle Rio had handed her and was quietly listening to their conversation.

“...” Rio denied nothing, remaining silent with a conflicted face.

“It’s a hardship, but wouldn’t it be easier to separate yourself from those close to you if that were the case? There’s no one close to you here in the Paladia Kingdom, no?” Duran appeared to be a brute military man, but he actually seemed to have a broad perspective and deep insight. Rio himself had also considered leaving those dear to him, after all.

“Indeed, you make a fair point.” Rio nodded with a strained smile.

“Right? Now that you’ve fulfilled your revenge, you need a new goal in your life. I’ll be able to provide you with one. Major nations are fussy about social status and tradition, but my kingdom will allow you to rise as far as your abilities extend. You can have any wish of yours fulfilled once you’re officially appointed.” Duran’s recruitment speech was truly persistent and skillful. He valued Rio highly and brought out all his favorable conditions at the perfect moments.

“It’s a very tempting proposal, but... I’m not sure about a life goal, but I do have somewhere I wish to return.”

Rio’s feelings hadn’t changed. The wariness he had at the beginning disappeared over the course of their conversation, and he found Duran to have a very charming personality, but the people he wanted to be with were somewhere else.

“So I cannot sway you...” Duran stared at Rio’s face, then sighed sadly.

“My apologies. If that’s all you wanted to discuss, I will be taking the two princesses into my care.” Rio glanced at Christina and Flora behind him.

“If you desire it, I can invite the three of you to my castle as guests.”

“I’m still technically an honorary knight of the Galarc Kingdom, and the two princesses cannot afford to create a debt to the kingdom allied with the Proxia Empire.”

“...Can you carry the two injured princesses alone?” Duran asked.

Rio returned the question boldly. “Did you think I couldn’t?”

“Goodness. There’s absolutely no weakness to pick at here. Should I just threaten you with the crime of ruining my kingdom’s land?” Duran argued back, though he didn’t have any intention of doing so.

“If you did, I’d threaten you back for the Paladia Kingdom’s involvement in abducting the two princesses...”

“I figured. Just so you know, it was Lucius who planned the whole thing. All I did was help Lucius face you after he had already kidnapped the princesses.”

“But you accepted the opportunity to receive one of the princesses as a reward, no?”

Duran chuckled. “That plan was suspended, but it sure makes me sound bad.”

“If you allow me to leave this place quietly, then I will personally refrain from making unnecessary statements regarding the Paladia Kingdom.” Rio presented a bargaining chip and glanced at Christina.

“...We will follow Sir Amakawa’s lead. As long as your side doesn’t act upon this incident, I do not intend on pursuing your kingdom for any further responsibility,” Christina said.

“Goodness... Ugh, fine. Do as you wish.” Duran ruffled his own hair in frustration.

“Thank you for your generous consideration.”

“Hmph. Just so you know, I’m unsatisfied with this. But if I cannot negotiate to bring you to my side, then I have no choice but to let you leave quietly. I already know what will happen if I try to stop you with force.”

“While this isn’t a trade by any means, feel free to take Lucius’s sword back with you.” Rio looked at Lucius’s sword, which was stabbed into the ground nearby.

Duran replied after a long pause. “...I see no reason for me to accept it. It’s the sword of the man you defeated, so it rightfully belongs to you.”

“I will conduct a minimal amount of cleanup, but I’ve caused a lot of trouble for this land and the village. Would you consider it compensation for that, as well as a bribe for your silence regarding my name?” Rio said, offering reasons for entrusting Lucius’s sword to Duran.

“I see...”

“That enchanted sword probably has the ability to release the wielder’s magic essence as slashing attacks, the ability to teleport the blade within one’s field of view, and the ability to teleport oneself within one’s field of view. If Your Highness is seeking military power, then it shouldn’t be a loss for you to keep.”

“Indeed, it isn’t a bad deal... But don’t you think it’s a little expensive for hush money? That’s probably a top-class enchanted sword, you know?” Duran said, laughing.

“I don’t mind. I have no interest in swinging around the sword of my enemy.” Just looking at the sword was enough to remind him of Lucius’s face.

“Hmm... Fine. I shall accept it.”

“Then it’s a deal.” Rio smiled in satisfaction, turning around as though to end the conversation.

“Wait,” Duran called Rio back.

“What is it?”

“This isn’t a recruitment, but a pure invitation—the next time we meet somewhere, have a meal with me as a friend.”

“A meal...as a friend?” Rio cocked his head curiously.

“I’m saying we’ll have drinks. Don’t tell me you can’t handle your alcohol?”

“No, I can drink in moderation...”

“Then it’s decided.” Duran smiled in high spirits.

“...All right.” He doubted they’d ever have such an opportunity, but there was nothing Rio could do but nod.

“Well then, I’ll be taking Lucius’s sword and leaving. I’m curious as to how you’ll go about cleaning this place up, but a promise is a promise.” Duran shrugged.

I don’t know what effect is instilled in his enchanted sword, but it’s probably that strange sorcery he used during his battle with Lucius. I’ll investigate that further the next time we meet, he thought to himself.

“Take care.”

Duran quietly walked over to where Lucius’s sword was stabbed into the ground and pulled it out. It was common courtesy to clean up after oneself, after all. He then turned and set off in the direction of the village. This left only Rio, Christina, and Flora behind.

Now, then...

Rio checked that Duran was out of sight, then drew his sword from its sheath. He stabbed it into the soil and poured magic essence into the ground through it. The ruined land started to stir as though it were alive. Dirt and stone wriggled until the land returned to a flat state.

“Wha...” Christina watched the sight with her jaw dropped. She had witnessed many outlandish sights during the battle with Lucius, but this was something to behold as well. This was something she couldn’t recreate with Strahl magic.

Rio adjusted the terrain in roughly ten seconds or so, then looked around the area. “...That should do,” he muttered, sheathing his sword back at his waist.

“...” Christina blinked at Rio’s face with wide eyes. He turned back to her.

“Sorry for the wait,” he said.

“Ah... R-Right,” Christina replied, snapping back to her senses.

“Can you stand up?” Rio offered Christina his hand.

“Yes...” Christina accepted his hand nervously and let him pull her onto her feet.

“That collar needs to be removed,” Rio said, reaching for her neck. Christina couldn’t see it happen, but his hand glowed faintly before the collar unlocked with a clack.

“It’s off.” Rio grabbed the collar and tossed it to the ground.

“Huh? Oh... Thank you very much.”

How did he do that without using disenchanting magic? That was the question clearly showing on Christina’s face. Confused, she reached up to confirm that the strangling sensation around her neck had disappeared.

“Are you hurt anywhere?”

“N-No. Everything’s healed thanks to the potion you gave me.”

“Great.”

“What about your injuries, Sir Amakawa? You said you at least stopped the bleeding...” Christina noted, worried about Rio’s injuries.

“Yes, it seems like the bleeding has stopped. There shouldn’t be a problem if I treat myself after I’ve transported the two of you, so we should get moving soon. I’ll get you to a place where you can rest peacefully—we can discuss everything else there.”

He could feel a dull pain, but the blood attached to his coat was already starting to dry. Rio touched the area that Lucius had cut as he thought to himself.

That aside, I hadn’t expected the black wyvern leather to be cut through so easily. I wonder if it can be fixed...

Lucius’s sword had the ability to teleport through space, so perhaps cutting through space itself had an effect on what the sword could slice through.

“You haven’t healed yourself yet, so you shouldn’t be moving around... Will you at least take the time to cast Cura properly before we depart?” Christina suggested worryingly.

“But we can’t stay here either, right? Prince Duran left, but there’s a possibility he might return to check the area. I won’t be moving that strenuously, and it’s only a short distance, so I’ll be fine.”

“In that case, allow me to treat you while we’re moving. I can use Cura, so...” Christina said with a frown as she suggested the second-best plan.

“No, I can cast healing magic myself while I move, so I’ll be fine.”

He needed to place his hand directly on the affected area in order to heal efficiently, but it was possible to stop his wound from bleeding without touching it while running or flying in a physically enhanced state. Because he had needed to use his spirit arts to continuously detect magic essence across a wide area to predict where Lucius would teleport during their battle, he hadn’t had the leisure to focus on healing. However, now he could spend that share of his focus on healing.

“No, please let me heal you. It isn’t enough to thank you, so I just want to do something—anything—for you. So, please... Allow me.” Christina lowered her head, pleading.

Rio looked up at the sky in discomfort. “I understand... In that case, could you please do so? And raise your head, please.”

“Thank you very much...” Christina’s voice and shoulders trembled as she kept her head bowed down.

Christina suggested a more objective method of checking.

“Y-Yes,” Flora nodded timidly.

“Come over here.”

“Okay...”

The two approached each other.

“I’m going to smell you then.”

“Please.”

After confirming with Flora, Christina brought her face towards Flora’s neck. However, when she took a sniff and looked in the direction of the changing room door, she saw Rio standing there with towels in hand.

“S-Sir Amakawa?!” Christina shrieked hysterically.

“Eek... That tickles, Christina. Hehe—S-Sir Haruto?!” Flora was trembling at the ticklish feeling when Christina’s outburst made her realize that Rio had returned. She panicked, flustered.

“Umm... Sorry for the wait,” Rio said awkwardly.

“I-It’s not what you think!”

“Y-Yes, it’s not what you think!”

The royal siblings clarified with shrill voices.

“Yes... I am aware.”

“A-Aware... Aware of what, may I ask...?”

“That the two of you are extremely close,” Rio replied with a smile.

“Erm... Y-You’re not wrong, but I apologize for acting so unsightly.” Christina’s head drooped, her face flushed. Flora’s face was similarly red, but she had completely frozen up.

Rio walked to the back of the changing room and put all the towels on the shelf. He then turned to leave, a slight smile in his voice. “I’ll leave the towels on this shelf, so please use them freely. Take your time.”

The changing room door closed, leaving Christina and Flora alone.

“...Shall we go inside?”

“Okay.”

With slightly bashful looks, the two started taking off their dresses.

◇　◇　◇

In the bathroom of the stone house, a splash echoed—it was the sound of Christina washing the shampoo out of her long hair.

With her social status being what it was, she normally had her servants wash it for her, but that didn’t mean she couldn’t wash it herself. She finished cleaning in roughly the same amount of time her servants usually took and placed the wooden bucket down on the floor.

“Just washing my hair is enough for me to feel refreshed...” Christina sighed dreamily.

Beside her, Flora was rubbing bubbles into her own hair. “Yes. This soap smells so nice and healing too.”

She brought her hair, which was covered in bubbles, up to her nose and sniffed it happily. This was probably why she had taken more time to wash herself than Christina.

“Wash up quickly or your body will get cold. You still haven’t fully recovered, remember?” Christina warned Flora while adding conditioner to her hair.

“R-Right.” Flora resumed washing her hair. Since it was so long, she had to be extra careful she hadn’t left any bubbles.

“Err, I believe this one was the face wash soap, right?”

Christina demonstrated her dexterity even here, applying conditioner to her hair and washing her face. She made sure to lather the soap before rubbing it on her face.

Ah, it feels so good...

She could tell her dry skin was rapidly absorbing the moisture. With her eyes closed, she basked in the bliss. Without using too much strength, she washed the dirt off her face, then washed off the bubbles.

“Ack! Are you washing your face already, Christina?” When Flora saw that, she rushed to use the bucket to wash out the shampoo in her hair.

“Make sure you wash off the bubbles properly. The warm water should heat up your body a bit, so there’s no need to rush,” Christina chuckled, then moved to wash her body last. She rubbed body soap into a hand towel to work it into a lather and started cleaning herself with her non-dominant hand.

It really is a lovely scent, though. I thought the best soaps out there were the ones developed by the Ricca Guild, but this soap foams wonderfully and smells good too...

There was no way of confirming how effective it was until she got out of the bath, but that was the impression Christina got.

Or is this soap also made by the Ricca Guild? Be it this house, or the space sorcery artifact that stored this house, Sir Amakawa’s belongings are shrouded in mystery too.

Christina turned her head and looked around the bathroom covered in stone. She’d been shown rare items she hadn’t witnessed before even as royalty, making it tough to stifle her curiosity completely.

That being said, Rio probably hadn’t wanted to show them this house—he hadn’t brought it out once on their journey from Cleia to Rodania. And the reason for that was clear: if word of it got out, everybody would want it. Soap aside, the space sorcery and magic artifacts in this house couldn’t be reproduced.

I’m curious about its origins, but I shouldn’t pry too much. Even if he tells me, it isn’t something that should be shared. I’d have to tell him I don’t intend on telling anyone else... Christina thought. Her hand moving the towel stopped and the scent of the body soap tickled her nose.

“It really smells wonderful...” she mumbled to herself, her mouth twisting in slight bitterness. It was the same scent she had smelled on Rio when he carried them to this house.

“Did you say something, sister?” Flora asked, massaging the conditioner into her hair before beginning to wash her face.

“No, it’s nothing. I’m almost done washing myself, but did you want me to wash your back for you?”

“Huh? Are you sure? Oh, but...” Flora’s face brightened, but she then looked at the stone bathtub. “Why don’t you take the chance to soak in the tub too?” she suggested.

“It’s fine. If you’re not getting in, I’d feel bad for doing so alone.”

“There’s no need to feel bad. I’d like to hear your thoughts on how it feels too. Please, give it a try on my behalf.” Flora looked at her older sister in anticipation.

“Really...? Then I’ll get in for a little bit... Just until you’re done washing, okay?”

“Yes! Please do!”

“Then, if you don’t mind.” Christina chuckled and stood up from the bath stool, touching the round stone to use the higher tap to wash the soap off of her body. She then stepped towards the bathtub.

It really is a huge bathtub...

It almost looked big enough to fit ten people in at once. Hot water poured out of the taps, constantly keeping the environment hygienic, according to Rio.

“Is it really hot?” Christina muttered, looking down at the steam rising from the water. Her naked figure was faintly reflected on the surface of the moving water.

“If I recall correctly, I’m meant to get in like this without a towel...”

She started by slowly dipping her right foot into the water, making a splashing sound as ripples spread across the surface.

“It’s hot...but not too hot to get in.” Christina continued by stepping into the bath with her left foot, then slowly sank into the water. The sensation of hot water wrapped around her body.

“Wow... I see, this is indeed...”

She closed her eyes until she got used to the temperature and relaxed her stiff body. It felt so good, she let out a blissful sigh.

“How is it, Christina?” Flora paused as she was about to wash her face and looked up curiously.

“It’s hot, and it feels great. I could get used to this,” Christina replied honestly.

“That’s great! I want to try getting in too.”

“You can once you’re fully recovered. Come on, your hands have stopped. Hurry up and finish washing. The bathroom is warm from the steam, but you’re still naked, so your body will get cold.”

“R-Right!” Flora moved her hands and finally began washing her face.

Good grief. But it seems like Sir Amakawa’s medicine is working well. Her complexion is clearly better than before.

While soaking in the tub, Christina gazed at Flora and thought to herself in exasperation. However, there was a faint smile on her face.

I’ve washed my hair already, so would it be best to leave it out of the water? Christina thought after a minute of watching Flora, and promptly scooped up her hair with her hands. Her thinking wasn’t wrong either—it was actually better to keep your hair out of the water, but Rio lacked that knowledge as a man and hadn’t explained it. Her hair had been floating on the surface of the water.

I’ll wrap it up with a towel.

She stood up abruptly, but she had stayed in the bath for too long and became dizzy.

“Wha...?!”

Christina was unable to support herself with her own legs and sank back into the water with a splash.

Wh-What?

Christina was confused. She had never experienced getting dizzy from a bath until now, so she felt uneasy.

“Christina?”

Flora had just finished washing her hair and body and noticed the abnormality. When she saw Christina stand up and sit back down right away, she called out to her.

“I felt dizzy for a moment...”

“Huh?! Are you okay?” Flora looked worriedly at Christina, who was pressing a hand to her forehead.

“Yes. If you’re done washing your body, let’s go out together.” Christina tried to stand up after saying that, but the dizziness made it impossible. Her vision blurred until it was nearly pure white, and her heart was racing in her chest.

“I-I’ll go call Sir Haruto!”

Flora was unable to contain herself and ran out of the changing room. She dried her body in a hurry and wrapped a towel around herself before opening the changing room door.

“U-Umm! Sir Haruto, are you there?” She called Rio’s name in a slightly louder voice.

Rio soon approached the changing room. “Princess Flora? Is something the matter...?” He froze when he spotted Flora in only a single bath towel and quickly averted his gaze.

“Ah. U-Umm, my sister isn’t feeling too well.” Flora noticed the state of her dress and blushed, but prioritized her report on her sister’s condition.

Rio’s expression immediately turned serious. “Princess Christina...? Is she still conscious?”

“Yes.”

“Then I’ll speak to her through the door of the changing room. Princess Flora, you should return to her side.”

“Understood.”

Flora promptly turned back to the bathroom. Rio waited until he heard the door of the bathroom open, then stepped into the changing room.

“Princess Christina, it’s Haruto,” Rio said through the door.

“S-Sir Amakawa. I apologize for creating a fuss,” Christina’s voice replied. Her tone helped Rio determine that it wasn’t an emergency.

“Not at all. May I ask what happened?”

“Umm, I was soaking in the bath when I suddenly felt extremely dizzy and my vision blurred, and I couldn’t stand up...”

Rio formed a hypothesis from Christina’s explanation. He believed the cause of her symptoms had yet to be resolved, but confirmed the situation with her. “You became dizzy after soaking in the bath... Are you still in the water now?”

“Y-Yes.” The reply came back through the echo of the bathroom.

Rio sighed in relief. “I’m sorry, my explanation was insufficient. In my opinion, I believe you’re experiencing bath dizziness. It’s only temporary, so there’s no need to worry about it.”

“Bath dizziness...?” Flora’s curious voice said. She seemed to be right on the other side of the door connecting the changing room to the bathroom.

“When you soak yourself in a hot bath, blood circulates in your body faster and rises to your head. The dizziness you feel is because of that. Did you perhaps try to stand up suddenly after soaking in the water?” Rio asked.

“I did...”

“I see. Your body was just surprised by the sudden change in blood pressure. It’s hard to notice when you’re in the bath since it feels so nice, but you can experience dizziness after just a minute or two. As long as you’re not unconscious, you can take your time getting out of the bath or sit on the edge until you cool down. It’s one of the tricks to taking a long bath, actually.” Rio explained the ways of dealing with dizziness and even gave advice for taking long baths on top of that.

“Is that so...? I’m so sorry for causing any trouble,” Christina apologized, her voice trembling in embarrassment. However, since soaking-style baths weren’t commonplace in the Strahl region, it was no wonder she hadn’t experienced such a condition before.

“No, it’s understandable since you’re not used to these types of baths. My explanation was lacking. Please take your time getting out.”

“I-I understand.”

“I’ll excuse myself now, then. I’ll prepare cold drinks and wait outside.”

With those words, Rio left the changing room behind him.

◇　◇　◇

Christina and Flora got out of the bath and changed into the dresses they were borrowing from the wardrobe room, then made their way to the living room.

The moment Christina saw Rio, she blushed and apologized for her earlier mistake. “I apologize for the trouble I caused you just now, Sir Amakawa.”

“Not at all—don’t let it bother you. It was my fault for not explaining things more. I should be the one apologizing.”

“No, I was the careless one.”

“Then let’s just say we should both move on.” They’d never be able to reach an agreement at this rate.

“I understand...” Christina bowed her head awkwardly.

“I’ve prepared cold drinks and some easy-to-digest food for your fatigue. It may not suit your tastes, but would you like to eat it? I’m going to go wash up myself now,” Rio said, looking around the dining table.

“We can wait until you’re done with your bath.”

“You probably won’t be able to relax with me around, so don’t worry about me. You can enjoy your time with your sister instead,” Rio said considerately.

“That isn’t the case, but...”

“I agree.”

Christina immediately denied it and Flora nodded firmly in agreement.

“I’m honored, but the food will go cold. Please eat it while it’s still warm.”

“I understand...”

“Thank you very much, Sir Haruto.”

Christina bowed, Flora following suit.

“If you’re tired, you can call it a day afterwards and sleep. The two rooms over there are guest rooms, so once you’re sleepy, you can use them as you wish.”

“We appreciate everything you’ve done for us.”

“Now, if you’d excuse me.” Rio left with those words.

He returned less than thirty minutes later, done with his bath. Christina and Flora had just finished eating. Flora was falling asleep on the spot, exhausted from the long day. Since the fatigue was clear on Christina’s face too, they decided to set aside the serious talk for the day and rest properly instead.

◇　◇　◇

Around noon of the same day, in the Rubia Kingdom bordering the southwest of Paladia, one boy slept on in the royal castle.

“...”

Beside the bed where Kikuchi Renji slept, First Princess Sylvie sat in a chair and gazed out the window. Just then, someone knocked on the door to the room.

“Enter,” Sylvie called towards the door.

The door was ajar to begin with, but it opened slowly at Sylvie’s voice. A female knight stood in the doorway—it was Elena, the commander of Sylvie’s personal guard.

Sylvie took one glance at Elena’s face. “Elena. What is it?”

“Your meal is ready. I came to show you to the dining hall.”

“No thanks. I have no appetite.”

Elena’s brows furrowed in worry for Sylvie. “You’ve already skipped breakfast today, and you barely ate anything last night.”

“I can’t help it if I don’t have an appetite,” Sylvie replied tiredly.

“In that case, please go outside and move around. There’s no appetite to be gained staying inside this room all day.”

“No. Renji might wake up while I’m gone.”

“Princess Sylvie, please leave the nursing to the servants. Why do you have to trouble yourself over a man like this...?” There was a tone of disapproval in Elena’s voice.

“You’re speaking out of line. Renji is a hero,” Sylvie said with a bitter smile.

“I still cannot believe that this man is a hero... His reckless actions placed Your Highnesses in so much danger,” Elena complained with a stern look.

It was three days ago that Renji had tailed Sylvie and Reiss, crashing her reunion with Estelle. There, Renji lost to Lucius and had his limbs cut off in what was a crushing defeat.

Renji had probably intervened thinking he was helping Sylvie by saving Estelle, but the situation wasn’t that simple. A small kingdom like Rubia couldn’t oppose a large nation like the Proxia Empire. It would be one thing to retrieve Estelle secretly, but rescuing the hostage in front of Reiss was equivalent to declaring war on the Proxia Empire.

In other words, Renji’s actions had been far too thoughtless. Because of his actions, Sylvie had been forced to make a choice—whether to oppose Proxia, or join sides with Proxia.

But Sylvie was unable to deny Proxia. She thrust aside Renji and left him to fight Lucius alone.

If I had chosen to fight alongside him and save Estelle...

Would the result have differed? Could Renji have avoided being defeated? These were the only thoughts that had filled her mind for the past three days.

“We would have eventually had to make a choice between siding with Galarc or crossing sides to Proxia. The fact our kingdom has changed sides is still unknown too—it’s merely an agreement between Reiss and me, so there’s still a chance of saving Estelle.” Sylvie’s mouth was twisted bitterly as she spoke.

“What if Reiss makes further demands next time, though? This man has also become part of the Proxia Empire. He made a pact with Reiss himself. If we are to face the Proxia Empire in the future, then this man...”

...May end up becoming your enemy. Are you sure? These were the words in Elena’s throat, but she swallowed them down with a sour look.

“Well, there’s no telling what will happen.” It almost sounded like there was resignation in Sylvie’s words, making Elena glare at Renji on the bed.

“...”

Elena hadn’t liked Renji from the beginning. Her first impression of him was the worst. He looked like a child on the outside, but on the inside he was an arrogant adventurer like any other. His manner of speaking had been impolite from the first time he met Sylvie and Estelle, but she could admit he had the strength to back up his attitude.

“Come to think of it, you mentioned a meal. I have no appetite, but could you bring some soup?” Sylvie seemed to notice Elena’s scowling and sighed as she changed the subject. She had just made up a reason for Elena to temporarily leave the room.

“Mm...” Renji suddenly groaned, his body trembling.

“Renji?”

Renji opened his eyes faintly at Sylvie’s voice. “Mmgh.”

“You’re finally awake,” Sylvie said and beamed.

“Syl...vie...? Guh...!” Renji snapped out of his daze as he recalled the events before he had passed out and shot up in bed. At the same time, he summoned his Divine Arms in his dominant hand and clutched it tightly.

“H-Hey! Renji! Calm down! Stop!” Sylvie said in a panic.

“Where...?” Renji asked, looking around the room nervously.

“A guest room of the Rubia Castle. Can you put away your weapon...the Divine Arms?” Sylvie said with a sigh.

“...” Renji silently made his halberd disappear.

Sylvie shrugged in exasperation. “If you can move that much, your body’s probably fine. The limbs that were severed have been restored perfectly.”

Meanwhile, Elena was watching Renji with a look of discontent.

“What happened...?” Renji asked in wonder, examining the presence of his cleanly reattached limbs.

“‘What happened,’ you say...?!” Elena immediately snapped in rage.

“Quiet, Elena. I didn’t give you permission to speak.”

Elena reluctantly heeded Sylvie’s warning. “My apologies...”

“Do you remember what happened before you lost consciousness?” Sylvie asked first.

Renji nodded with a frown. “Yeah...”

“Your limbs were cut off, and you lost to Lucius. The shock of the blood loss left you unconscious for three days, but now you’re awake.” Sylvie summarized the events in a frank and concise manner.

“How were my limbs reattached?” Renji asked in confusion.

“It was apparently the work of the Divine Arms. An ability activated to keep you alive, but I don’t know the details as to how that happened either.”

“I see...”

“Any other questions?”

“Where are they now...?” Renji asked nervously. He was referring to Reiss and Lucius.

“They returned to the Proxia Empire. Do you remember your pact with Reiss before your battle?”

“...” Renji fell silent with an awfully uncomfortable look. He remembered.

“You’ve become a subordinate of Proxia... No, of Reiss. You can stay in this castle until he comes for you, but once he comes you must follow his orders,” Sylvie stated flatly.

“...” Renji frowned.

“Don’t tell me you intend on going back on your word.”

“Is it worth keeping a promise with people like them?” Renji replied to Sylvie, ashamed.

“I heard you often picked fights with the adventurers who looked down on you,” Sylvie said, abruptly changing the topic.

Two sides presented something important to them, and the victor obtained both—those were the basics of a duel. Royalty and nobility didn’t perform them thoughtlessly, but they were a frequent occurrence amongst hasty adventurers. Renji defeated anyone who picked a fight with him through duels, taking his opponents’ fortunes as a warning to others. That was how rumors of Renji spread, which greatly reduced the number of ruffians who looked down on him.

“Yeah...?” Renji nodded, slightly confused. He couldn’t figure out why duels were being mentioned.

“Have you ever let anyone you defeated go against their word?”

At Sylvie’s question, he finally understood her point. “No.”

Renji recalled how he stripped everyone he defeated of their fortunes mercilessly and awkwardly averted his eyes from Sylvie.

“In other words, you’ll make anyone weaker than you obey, but you’ll break your word against someone stronger? You’re running away?” Sylvie stared at Renji with a look of disdain.

“Uh...” Unable to make eye contact, Renji flinched.

“Pathetic. I liked your rebellious spirit towards the injustices of the world, but it seems like I misjudged you. You’re just a coward who can only act big before the weak—an outcast of society. You’re nothing but a lawless brat.”

“...” Her mocking tone made Renji clench his teeth, eyes still cast downwards.

“What’s wrong? Nothing to say for yourself? Wasn’t it your motto not to forgive those who look down on you? Who was it who spoke to a princess on an equal level the first time he met her?”

“...” With his head still bowed, Renji clenched his fists.

“I’m looking down on you right now, you realize? Same with Elena over there. She scoffs whenever she looks at you,” Sylvie said, looking at Elena. Elena purposefully scoffed so that Renji could hear, finding satisfaction in doing so.

Renji finally snapped. “Why are you saying this?”

“Why, you ask? After all the trouble you’ve caused me, you think I don’t have the right to voice my complaints?”

Despite being sullen, Renji raised his voice to make his point. “I-I was just trying to save Estelle. If you’re saying I ran away, then you’re a coward who couldn’t save Estelle too.”

Sylvie gave an undaunted reply, acknowledging her own cowardice. “Yes, that’s right. But I don’t intend to run from Reiss like you. I have to bear the burden of not just Estelle, but the entire kingdom. There’s no way I can run.”

“I-I tried to save her. But you sided with Reiss...” Renji implicitly placed the blame on Sylvie—that it was all because she did nothing.

Sylvie grit her teeth, harshening her tone as she scolded him. “The situation’s taken a troublesome turn because of your reckless savagery. Reiss is backed by a large nation called the Proxia Empire. If I had opposed him there, they would eventually confront our kingdom. Are you telling our small kingdom to face a major nation? Or would you fight the Proxia Empire alongside us? You, a man who would run away from your promise with Reiss, wouldn’t run from a war with his empire?”

“I-I... I didn’t know he was backed by the Proxia Empire.”

“I called you a savage because you meddled in my business without knowing anything. Reiss and Lucius mentioned it before the duel—you’ve grown arrogant in thinking that everything can be solved with your strength, haven’t you?”

“...” He couldn’t deny it. He wanted to argue for himself, but he couldn’t find the words. The one defense he had on the tip of his tongue was that it was an overstatement, but it was so pathetic that he swallowed it back down.

“Coward. Where did the self-righteous man I know go? I guess the attitude was just a facade and this is your true self, huh?” Sylvie sighed in heavy disappointment.

“I...!” Renji raised his head to object, but when he noticed Sylvie staring back at him he quickly looked down again.

“So pathetic... Enough. Leave this castle—no, leave the kingdom. You’re an eyesore,” Sylvie spat coldly.

Elena was shocked. “P-Princess Sylvie?! What about your agreement with Reiss? You can’t leave this man to his own devices.”

Sylvie waved her hand in irritation. “I don’t care. He’s such an eyesore. I’ll come up with an explanation for Reiss and Lucius later.”

“...” Renji didn’t stand. He was still sitting up in the bed, clenching the sheets in both fists as he worked through his inner conflict.

“What? Get out already. Or are you asking to be cut down here?” Sylvie jeered.

“I... I’m...” Renji murmured.

Sylvie looked at him warily. “What?”

“I’m sorry... You’re right. I have no excuse,” Renji said at an audible volume.

“So what?” Sylvie asked in a detached tone.

“Please allow me to assist in Estelle’s rescue. You want to save her too, right? I’ll do anything I can to help. I’ll atone for my failure after she’s rescued.” Renji’s reply took on a rather meek attitude. It was a look that actually fit the age of the boy Sylvie first met.

After a dazed pause, Sylvie burst out laughing. “Ha! Ha ha ha! So you have the capacity to make a face like that?”

“Don’t make fun of me; I’m being serious,” Renji said, biting down on his lip.

“Sorry,” Sylvie said with a wry smile, then changed her tone to a gentle one. “But your assistance is unnecessary. I appreciate the sentiment, but you really should leave.”

“Wh-Why...?” Renji asked, confused.

“You wield tremendous power, but you’re fatally lacking something. I’ve always found that strange, but that was also the part of you I was drawn to. And yet, the answer was surprisingly simple. For better or for worse, you’re still a child. I realized that today. That’s why I can’t allow you to get involved,” Sylvie warned.

“That’s not true! I’m seventeen!” Renji yelled.

While it wasn’t the case in Japan, seventeen-year-olds were formally treated as adults in this world. Sylvie herself was eighteen, which was why Renji based his argument around his age.

“The way you bring up your age only makes you more childish.”

“Y-You’re wrong! Don’t treat me like a kid!”

“I’m not. You force others to take responsibility while lacking any sense of responsibility yourself. That’s what makes you a child.”

“That’s not...!”

“You’re trying to break your promise with Reiss right this moment.”

“That’s... I...” Renji stumbled for something to say in protest.

“Listen, Renji. This is a warning. You’re just a child bestowed with an incredible power through no effort of your own—it’s all the work of the Divine Arms. That’s why you’re all mixed up,” Sylvie stated bluntly. “You live within society while shirking all social obligations. You only participate in society when it benefits you—when it doesn’t, you exert your power to bend things your way. That’s how you’ve been living all this time, but you’ve finally encountered someone that won’t work on. Did you think you could live like that forever?” she said angrily to intimidate him.

“...” Renji gulped silently.

“There are people stronger than you—you’ve already lost to one of them. Just because you’re strong as an individual doesn’t mean you can underestimate the power of the masses. I’m going to teach you that lesson right now.”

“...Huh?” Renji looked confused, wondering how she would do that.

“For your grave crimes against the kingdom, I declare you an enemy of Rubia as of today. You may no longer live in this kingdom from here on out.”

“Wha...” Renji fell speechless at the sudden declaration.

“However, I will atone for my share of the blame. This is my final act of kindness—I shall allow you to flee. So leave this castle now,” Sylvie declared.

“...” Renji remained frozen on the bed.

“What’s wrong? Why aren’t you leaving?” Sylvie asked unhappily.

Renji finally raised his voice. “W-Wait a moment, please! I can’t do that, Sylvie!”

“Why not?” Sylvie asked with a fed up expression.

“I’ve realized it thanks to your words—if I flee now, I’ll regret it forever! I’ll no longer be myself! That’s what I feel! I have to defeat Lucius in order to move forward with my life!”

Sylvie’s expression wavered for a brief moment during Renji’s desperate pleas, but she quickly gathered herself and shook her head. “That’s your own personal business. It has nothing to do with us.”

“B-But you need my power, right?! That’s right... My power will be beneficial for this kingdom. Because I’m a hero,” Renji said without a care for how it made him sound.

“It’s not your power, but the power of the Divine Arms... That petty pride of yours is what I’m calling childish.”

“Then I’ll become an adult! I won’t screw up next time! Please believe me!” Renji protested stubbornly.

“Don’t assume there’ll always be a next time. And believe you? Do you really think I can believe in the way you are now?” Sylvie said, giving Renji a cold dose of reality by pointing out his arrogance.

“Uhm...” Renji gulped.

“That’s all I have to say. Get out. And never step foot into this capital—no, this kingdom again. The next time I see your face in our lands, I will cut you down without mercy. So be prepared,” Sylvie threatened.

Renji was at a loss for words. “Are you serious...?” he asked, trembling.

“Yes, I am. So leave.” Sylvie nodded without hesitation, pointing at the open door.

“I... I won’t,” Renji declared. His eyes were bloodshot and his breathing harsh.

“What?”

“I won’t leave this place,” Renji repeated clearly.

“Renji, you...” Sylvie said, clearly displeased.

“If I stay in the kingdom after leaving this castle I’ll be cut down, right? Then I won’t leave. You won’t cut me down if I don’t leave, right?”

“You think your shoddy logic will work on me?!” Sylvie shot to her feet with a fierce look, reaching for her sword resting nearby.

“P-Princess Sylvie.” Elena quickly grabbed Sylvie’s arm and blocked her with her own body.

“Let go, Elena!”

“I-I will not!”

Sylvie and Elena argued back and forth, while Renji spoke up beside them.

“I’m not leaving this castle,” Renji declared sullenly.

“You child... Are you saying you’ll become Reiss’s subordinate, then?!” Sylvie yelled.

“If that’s taking responsibility as an adult, then yes,” Renji replied with a frown.

“Ngh... Do what you want! Release me, Elena!” Sylvie grimaced bitterly and gave in out of frustration. She sheathed her sword and shoved aside Elena’s clinging grip before marching out of the room.

“P-Please wait a moment, Princess Sylvie!” Elena said and hurried after her.

◇　◇　◇

In an uninhabited area of the Paladia Kingdom, just after Rio left the outskirts of the village where he killed Lucius and invited Christina and Flora into his stone house...

There was someone observing from above. Reiss. He had shadowed Rio as he carried Christina and Flora away from the village where he had dueled Lucius to the death.

If he’s brought out his house, then he won’t be traveling again today. Princess Flora seemed rather exhausted, so he must be prioritizing her recovery, Reiss surmised to himself from where he looked down on the house.

That aside, how shall I act next? With the option to coordinate with Lucius gone, I have no choice but to give up on dealing with Haruto. The risks of making a move outweigh the risks of leaving him be, but letting him return without any resistance at all...

It felt humiliating. The mess that Lucius made had left Reiss in a very troubling situation.

What would happen if he allowed Rio and the princesses to return like this? What kind of information would reach the Restoration and Galarc, and how would they react? Reiss considered the possibilities.

There’s no hiding the fact it was Lucius who abducted Beltrum’s royal princesses. It’s also common knowledge that Lucius had connections with the ambassador of the Proxia Empire—with me. Considering the fact that I was spotted in Rodania just before the royal siblings went missing, then...

The abduction of Christina and Flora would most likely be deemed the work of the Proxia Empire. If he was unlucky enough, his connections to the Duke Arbor faction could be raised as well.

While there’s nothing that can be done about Galarc and the Restoration’s increased wariness towards Proxia, the risk and return will be far too unbalanced if things go on at this rate. The only thing that was gained in all this is my faked death, and I don’t even know if that spirit was fooled...

During the battle at Rodania’s outskirts, Reiss had made it look like Aishia cornered and defeated him. He had actually summoned a monster to be killed in his place, helping him escape successfully.

I cannot appear before Haruto right now. If me faking my death actually went as planned, then his attention will be directed away from me. It would be a waste to discard that advantage here. Which means I’ll have to send the squad members to make up for the failures of their commander. They can think of it as a way to get revenge for him.

There were only two problems with that—the first being what kind of situation he wanted to create with them.

However, Princess Sylvie should come to terms with her situation soon, and I’ve obtained a new pawn to replace the old one, so perhaps I can make a scapegoat out of him instead.

Reiss immediately came up with a good plan and grinned wickedly.

The remaining problem is where to make them face each other, but they should be heading for either Rodania or Galarc. Whichever way they go, they’ll have to pass through the Rubia Kingdom. The window of opportunity will be extremely limited if he flies with the two princesses, but I’ll endeavor to arrange something.

Since it was an ironclad law to only travel during daylight, he’d spend his daytime hours tracking Rio. If he needed to give orders and move personnel, he’d do that after Rio had stopped moving to rest.

I guess I’ll head over to Arein and the others after marking this location.

With that decided, Reiss descended to the ground.

◇　◇　◇

Roughly ten or so minutes later, Reiss used a single-use teleportation crystal to relocate immediately. He reappeared elsewhere in the Paladia Kingdom, in a deserted village just a few dozen kilometers away from where Rio had set up his stone house.

“Now...” With no hesitation in his steps, Reiss marched forward. He stopped before a run-down house that would’ve belonged to the past village chief and knocked on the door in a particular rhythm. Soon after he did, the door to the house flew open. It seemed like the occupant was feeling rather hasty.

“Why, Mister Reiss...”

Sure enough, the one who opened the door was Arein, Lucius’s subordinate. Lucci and Ven stood immediately behind him.

“The three of you look well,” Reiss said with an unreadable smile.

“Umm... The captain isn’t with you?” Arein asked, examining Reiss’s expression before looking around for anyone accompanying him. As his question implied, he was wondering about Lucius’s whereabouts.

This deserted village was originally meant to be the meetup point after the plan was completed, but Reiss already visited two days ago after he escaped from Aishia. He had been seeking information from Arein and the others. However, he hadn’t been aware that Christina and Flora had been abducted at the time—he only found out when he arrived at the battlefield—and had no choice but to prioritize his meeting with Duran.

Consequently, Arein’s side hid in the village for two days, believing Lucius would return victorious.

“He was killed,” Reiss stated simply.

“...”

The faces of the three men stiffened—their expressions were of disbelief, clearly in denial of the truth. Reiss repeated himself once more, leaving no room for doubt.

“I said, Lucius is dead. He fought his fated enemy and, regrettably, lost,” he said with a heavy sigh.

“What kind of a joke is that? The captain was killed? Don’t make me laugh.” Lucci laughed dryly, but his smile didn’t reach his eyes.

“It’s not a joke,” Reiss said with a straight face.

“That’s impossible!” Lucci yelled. The walls of the house were made of dampened wood, yet his voice echoed loudly.

“There’s no need to yell,” Arein muttered with an annoyed look.

“Shut up! It’s the captain we’re talking about, okay?! And he’s supposed to be dead?! No, it has to be a joke. The captain wouldn’t kick the bucket so easily!” Lucci stubbornly refused to accept the truth.

“...”

Arein and Ven both fell silent, clenching their teeth.

“It’s a lie. It has to be,” Lucci muttered. His body was trembling slightly.

“Like I said before, two days ago, Lucius suddenly acted on his own. You claimed you had no idea where he went, but you actually knew all along, didn’t you?” Reiss suddenly asked, looking around at the three men.

“...”

Lucci was still shaking with his eyes fixed on the floor, but Arein and Ven exchanged a secretive look with each other.

“There’s no point in hiding it. I already know that Princess Christina and Princess Flora were abducted as hostages to be used against the boy. Considering the situation, you three are the only people who could have cooperated with him. I have no intention of blaming you. I just want to confirm the truth,” Reiss explained tiredly, implicitly urging them to come clean already.

Arein and Ven gave in with a guilty look. “Well, yeah. We prioritized the captain’s orders.”

“The three of you were originally his subordinates, after all. It makes sense. However, things may have ended differently if you had cooperated with me instead of him—I’d like you to keep that thought in mind.”

Reiss implicitly suggested that Lucius wouldn’t have died if they had obeyed his orders.

“Guh...”

Arein and Ven averted their eyes awkwardly. They had believed in Lucius’s clear victory. They had followed his orders under that belief, but the reality waiting for them was cruel.

“There was a beauty in the way that he was always victorious. He may have used cowardly tricks, but he was strong precisely because he didn’t hesitate to use those tricks. But the defeated are worthless. That was his belief, and he followed that belief to rise to the peak of all mercenaries. Now that he has lost, he’s become nothing more than a coward. He wasn’t strong because he was cowardly, but a coward because he was weak. That’s all there is to it, I suppose,” Reiss lamented in a dramatic tone.

“That’s not true!” Lucci suddenly yelled, eyes widening with rage.

“What isn’t?”

“The captain isn’t weak. He wasn’t a coward because he was weak...” Lucci’s voice trembled.

“Can you prove that?” Reiss asked.

There was no way of proving it—it was an instance of the devil’s proof.

“We’ll win. The captain’s Heavenly Lions will never lose. We haven’t lost to that boy as a mercenary squad yet—so we’ll win. We can prove the captain’s strength that way.” Lucci breathed heavily through his nose. Then, a slow clap echoed around them—it was the sound of Reiss clapping.

“Wonderful. In that case, may I place a request with the members of the Heavenly Lions before me? My request won’t be for you to win against the boy, but it will include combat against him. Does that sound interesting to you?”

Arein and Ven exchanged frowns. Rio was the one who killed Lucius—he had also crossed swords with Arein’s group before, and they were fully aware of the gap in their abilities. They weren’t intimidated, but they knew they couldn’t accept the request so easily.

“Are we not allowed to dispose of him, Mister Reiss?” Lucci asked with a glare.

“You’re free to eliminate him, of course. My request will be completed the moment you engage him in combat, but you’re most welcome to go further.”

“Then we’ll accept that request.”

“Hey, Lucci. You haven’t even heard the terms yet...” Ven scolded with a sigh.

“What? It’s a fight for revenge over what happened to the captain. Are you chickening out?” Lucci said, completely raring to go.

“Fool. Did you forget how easily we were brushed aside before? This is the bastard that killed the captain. I just don’t want to underestimate him,” Ven scoffed in disgust.

“There’s one thing I want to confirm first,” Arein said to Reiss, ruffling his own hair. “It sounds like you’re asking for this as a separate request from our tasks for the Proxia Empire. Is that right?”

The men were officially mercenaries of the Heavenly Lions, but during times of peace, they were paid to use their abilities as covert agents for Reiss.

“Yes. This is a fight to avenge Lucius, after all. You will be rewarded appropriately based on your results. I don’t mind entrusting you with the enchanted sword I had lent him either. It’s somewhat of a memento for you, no?” Reiss looked around at them and chuckled.

“We can’t say no to that,” Lucci said with an aggressive smile, looking at Arein and Ven.

“Let’s listen to the details first.” Arein sighed, deciding to give in.

Chapter 5: Departure and Pursuit

Three days passed since Rio invited Christina and Flora into the stone house, and five days since the two disappeared. Flora’s condition had fully recovered, and it was finally time for them to depart for Galarc.

“Conditum.”

They exited the stone house in the morning, and Rio chanted the spell to store the stone house back in the Time-Space Cache. The air distorted, making the huge boulder disappear in an instant.

“...”

Christina and Flora blinked in surprise. The Time-Space Cache had been explained to them at some point during the past three days, but the reality of it was so detached from what seemed like common sense, they still had trouble accepting what they saw.

Rio turned back around to them. “Shall we go, then?”

“Okay.”

“Thank you for your help, Sir Haruto.”

Christina and Flora both bowed their heads.

“I’ll carry you in the same way as I did three days ago... Is that okay?” Rio confirmed with Christina. In other words, Rio would carry Christina on his back and Flora in his arms.

“I don’t mind...” Christina nodded with a faint blush, recalling the time she had clung to Rio’s back.

“Speaking of which, how did you carry us here?” Flora had been unconscious until they entered the stone house, so she cocked her head curiously.

“Respectfully, I carried Princess Christina on my back and Your Highness in my arms. Would you be okay with a similar arrangement this time?” Rio explained to Flora.

“H-Huh? Oh, b-but... Right. O-Okay. That’s fine.” Flora blushed bright red in surprise, but she soon realized there would’ve been no other way for her to be carried. In fact, she had been carried similarly back when Lucius abducted her in Amande, so there wasn’t anything for her to be shocked about. Though, it was still embarrassing.

“Well, there’s no point in standing around forever. Princess Christina, please get on first,” Rio said, offering his back to Christina.

“Right... Excuse me.” With a faint blush on her cheeks, Christina climbed onto Rio’s back.

It should be fine today. I took a bath this morning, so there’s no need to be worried about my scent, she thought to herself. Even if she had to cling to Rio’s back, she wouldn’t have to lament over the same thoughts that plagued her three days ago. However, she was still extremely nervous. Would he be able to feel her heartbeat? That was one worry that rose within her.

Now that I think about it, in this position, my chest is constantly pressed up against Sir Amakawa’s back...

She was wearing a thin dress right now, so the sensation was more obvious than the gown she wore three days ago.

Th-That should be okay, right? I’m not that big to begin with... Yeah, it’s better off this way. Flora’s bigger than me, after all...

Christina’s face stiffened in a blush, her body freezing where it was pressed up against Rio’s back.

“Princess Flora—you’re next.”

“R-Right.”

“I’m going to pick you up,” Rio said, bending forward a little to place his arms under Flora’s back and knees to scoop her up lightly.

Flora blushed, looking down as she lay in Rio’s arms. “Eek... A-Am I heavy?”

“Not at all. Your Highnesses are both very light.”

“Thank goodness...” Flora sighed in relief.

“...” In contrast, Christina clung closely to Rio’s back in silence.

“I won’t go too quickly, but please hold on tight so you don’t get thrown off.”

“Okay!” Flora replied shyly but energetically.

For the record, the coat made of Black Wyvern leather had been ripped in several places during his fight with Lucius, so Rio had swapped it out for another coat. Flora grabbed on to it.

“Umm, I don’t mind if you grab my coat, but it’d probably be safer if you held on to me,” Rio pointed out awkwardly. If she didn’t secure her upper body by holding on to him, she could be jostled quite a bit by any sudden movements.

“Wha...? Oh, o-okay! L-Like this?” Flora nervously wrapped her arms around him.

“Flora, move your hands to where my stomach is,” Christina said from Rio’s back.

“Thank you, Christina.” Flora rested her face in Rio’s chest and wrapped her arms around his back.

We must look like quite the sight... Rio thought to himself, making an awkward face. If he lowered his gaze a little he’d see Flora’s face, and Christina’s breath was against his neck, tickling him slightly. But he couldn’t let it bother him—there was no other reasonable way of carrying them.

“That should be fine. Now, let’s get going—first stop, the Rubia Kingdom.”

It was an effort to just depart, but Rio managed to set off. He kicked off the ground and it was like his feet had grown wings, lifting him into the air at a leisurely speed. The scenery around them changed in a blink of an eye.

“W-Wow! This is amazing, Sir Haruto!” Flora yelled in excitement.

Meanwhile, Christina—who had enjoyed the same scenery three days ago—was just as wide-eyed again.

“Truly, it’s beautiful... It’s a different view than what you’d see in the airship,” she muttered in a daze.

“I’ll be moving at this speed, but let me know if it’s too fast.”

Their current speed was roughly thirty kilometers per hour. It wasn’t as fast as Rio’s running speed, but it felt faster than it actually was. The princesses weren’t used to flying, so this speed should’ve been just right for them.

“I’m fine.”

“Right.”

The two of them looked around the sky in great interest as they replied, seemingly comfortable.

“Please do enjoy the journey from the sky, then.”

Thus, Rio and the girls departed for the capital of the Galarc Kingdom without any issues. Or, so they thought.

“Well, then. It’s time for me to go too.”

Observing just one kilometer away from them was Reiss, who began his pursuit.

◇　◇　◇

The journey through the sky continued several hours later, with Rio descending regularly to allow Christina and Flora to rest on the ground.

The frequent breaks were partially for Christina and Flora, and partially because the two of them didn’t know the exact amount of magic essence that Rio had. He had explained spirit arts to them, but he hadn’t told them his essence was practically limitless. They would have noticed he had a tremendous amount of essence from the many spirit arts he used during his battle with Lucius, but he hadn’t explained anything to them.

“We’ll be crossing the Rubia border soon. Let’s enter the next city we see to get an accurate grasp of our location,” Rio said to the two of them as he flew.

“Okay. If it’s a city, it should have a magic artifact for transmission, so we can head for the governor’s estate as soon as we confirm we’re within Rubia,” Christina said, proposing a plan for once they arrived in the city.

“Understood.”

It was mere minutes later that they spotted a city in the direction Rio was flying. It appeared to be a fortress city—it was surrounded by stone walls and a fort-like building stood in the center.

“I’m thinking of landing there. Does that sound good to everyone?” Rio asked Christina.

“Yes please.”

“All right. I can’t land in the middle of the city, so we’ll be descending by the road. It’ll be a short walk, so please bear that in mind,” Rio said, then began his descent to the road.

◇　◇　◇

After a short walk down the road, the group arrived at the fortress city and immediately headed for the fort. It was a city in a small kingdom, so it wasn’t that large. They reached the fort after only a few minutes of walking. Rio led the way, followed by Christina and Flora. There were three guards in front of the gate, and one of them called out to them as they approached.

“Stop. Outsiders aren’t allowed past this point. This isn’t a tourist spot. Leave.”

Naturally, they were turned away at the door.

“I am Haruto Amakawa, honorary knight of the Galarc Kingdom, ally of Rubia. I wish to meet the governor. Can you pass on that message?” he said, having no set appointment. The guards exchanged looks with each other.

“P-Please wait a moment...”

The three guards turned their backs on them and started whispering to each other. Rio and the princesses were currently wearing casual travel clothes, so they didn’t look like nobility. But the guards’ reactions changed the moment Rio announced his title.

“Hey, isn’t the Galarc Kingdom...”

“It’s one of our allies, like he said. A huge one too.”

“Upon closer inspection, the girls behind him are really cute as well. They must be noble ladies or something.”

“Would it be better to let them in, then?”

“Yeah. But we’ll need some kind of identification first.”

The guards whispered back and forth to each other in a short amount of time, before they whipped back around and questioned Rio politely.

“Thank you for waiting. Do you have any proof of your identity?”

“Yes. This is the emblem His Majesty bestowed me.”

Rio took the emblem out of his breast pocket and showed it to them. The guards didn’t know what the crest of Galarc’s royal family looked like, but it was clearly an expensive object, so they deemed it to be authentic.

“Indeed, this will do. Who are the other two?”

“They are the ladies of high rank that I am escorting.”

In order to avoid causing a scene, Rio avoided revealing them as Beltrum’s royal sisters.

The guards exchanged another look with each other and one stepped out to guide them. “Please, come on through. I shall show you the way.”

“My apologies for the trouble.” Rio bowed politely and followed the guard leading the way. Christina and Flora continued after him. The two remaining guards stole glances at the girls as they passed.

“Hey... Did you see that?”

“Y-Yeah. I’ve never seen such beautiful girls before.”

“Their hair was the same color and their faces looked similar... Could they be sisters?”

“Perhaps.”

There wasn’t much to gossip about in a fortress city in the countryside, and the guards had a very idle job. There were even some days where no one visited the fort. Thus, the two guards left behind started chatting to each other in excitement at the beauty of Christina and Flora.

However, as soon as Rio and the others were out of sight, another person approached the gate. It was Reiss. The two guards began whispering to each other.

“Hey, someone else is here.”

“You’re right. He looks like a traveler, but there’s something creepy about him.”

During that time, Reiss came up to them.

“Hello. I’m Jean Bernard, advisor to Princess Sylvie and a noble of the royal court.”

In order to enter the fort after Rio, Reiss revealed his position in the Rubia Kingdom.

◇　◇　◇

Rio and the princesses were led to a drawing room of the fort. The three sat down on the sofa and waited.

“Hello, hello, I’m sorry for the wait. I heard Galarc’s honorary knight was here? I’m the governor of this city, Marco Tonteri. I believe you said your name was...”

The door to the drawing room opened to reveal a plump man in his middle years. There was a layer of sweat over his forehead as he humbly sought a handshake from Rio first. When he spotted Christina and Flora, a faint light sparkled in his eye.

Rio stood up to accept the handshake from Marco. “Haruto Amakawa. I apologize for visiting unannounced.”

“Not at all. What business would an esteemed honorary knight have with a governor of the countryside like me?” Marco cocked his head in wonder. He glanced at Christina and Flora, who flanked Rio’s sides on the sofa.

“I have an urgent message I need to send to the capital of the Galarc Kingdom. May I use the transmitter in this city to contact the capital?” Rio asked.

“I see. If it’s the request of an honorary knight from an ally, then it would be my honor,” Marco agreed easily.

“Thank you very much. If I may ask, how long does it take for a message to reach Galarc from Rubia?”

“The message can arrive as early as today, but if you’re expecting a reply from the other side, then it will probably arrive tomorrow...”

If the message Rio was about to send reached Galarc’s royal castle, there was no way for Galarc to confirm the truth of the message. Since the receiver wouldn’t be able to verify the identity of the sender, the credibility of the message was an issue.

That being said, neither Galarc nor the Restoration would be able to ignore any news of Christina and Flora in their current state, so it would at least delay things from taking an unhelpful turn before they could make it back.

It was already afternoon. Sunset was still a fair way off, but it would start to darken in a few hours, so it would be strange for them to leave the city at this hour to continue their journey.

“In that case, may I visit the fort again tomorrow morning?”

They could afford to wait one night for a reply from the Galarc Castle before departing in the morning.

“Of course—that wouldn’t be a problem. Do you have any plans after this?”

“Not in particular. I’m actually in the middle of escorting these two ladies on a journey, but we won’t be traveling further today, so I was thinking of finding an inn for us.”

“I shall refrain from prying further, as it seems you have your own circumstances you’re dealing with... I cannot allow our guests from Galarc to go without shelter, but I’m afraid this fort isn’t furnished with guest rooms for nobility. I shall arrange accommodations for you at an inn, so please stay there,” Marco offered. Christina had explained on the road that it was noble etiquette to accept accommodation offers from a host if you didn’t have a prior arrangement—even though it would be more comfortable to stay outside the city in the stone house.

“We’ll accept your kind offer.” Rio bowed.

“It’s a simple city with nothing to see, so allow me to prepare some entertainment for you after you have finished sending your message. Would you like to join me for dinner?”

“Yes, thank you very much for the offer.”

He wasn’t very comfortable with talking to an unfamiliar noble, but declining the offer of someone doing them a favor would be rude. Besides, Marco had an overwhelming lack of information regarding Rio’s party. They managed to get this far smoothly just by the possibility of Rio being an honorary knight of a large allied nation, but Marco probably wanted to know a bit more.

If Rio rejected him here, they would seem suspicious. A conversation with Marco was unavoidable.

“Now, please write your message down on this paper. Ah, I’m sure you’re aware of this already, but transmission artifacts can only send a maximum of one hundred letters at a time, so please keep that in mind.” Marco handed Rio writing tools and paper for him to write his message.

“Thank you very much. If you don’t mind...”

Rio must have had his message decided in advance, as his hand moved without pause.

King Francois.

The two VIPs you want are safe. On the way back now.

Honorary Knight Haruto Amakawa.

“Please send this.” Rio held the paper out to Marco.

“Understood.” Marco accepted the paper and read over the words carefully. There was nothing written that shouldn’t be read—the message was going to be revealed to every city along the transmission line anyway, so there was nothing to worry about there.

Just then, a knock came.

“Excuse me.” A soldier of the fort hurried inside.

“I’m in the middle of a meeting with an important guest here.” Marco glared at the soldier to scold his lack of consideration.

“M-My sincerest apologies. There is a matter requiring your urgent attention, Sir.” The guard approached Marco in his chair beside the doorway and started whispering in his ear.

“What...? Ugh, all right. I’ll be there immediately.”

Marco puffed up with a sullen look and sighed. “I’m sorry to interrupt our conversation, Sir Amakawa—I haven’t even greeted your two acquaintances properly yet. I’m afraid some urgent business has come up.”

He bowed his head to his guests across from him.

“No, I’m sure you have many duties as a governor. We’re the ones who intruded without warning, so please prioritize your work,” Rio said on behalf of his side.

“Much obliged. I shall return after sending this message. Would you be all right with relaxing in this room until I am done?” Marco folded the paper and put it in his pocket.

“Yes, we would be happy to. Thank you for attending to the message.” Staying in the room would be the least tiring option for Rio and the girls.

“Please excuse me.”

With those words, Marco left the room with the soldier.

◇　◇　◇

Marco exited the drawing room, leaving Rio and the girls behind. As soon as he did so, he was approached by the figure waiting in the hallway.

“Long time no see, Lord Tonteri.”

“Why, if it isn’t Sir Jean Bernard. It’s been a while,” Marco said.

It was Reiss, though he was using the alias of a Rubian noble named Jean Bernard.

“My apologies for calling you out in the middle of a meeting,” Reiss apologized politely.

“Not at all. What business would a noble of Princess Sylvie’s court have here?”

“I have something to discuss with you regarding the guests you were just dealing with.”

“Is that so?” Marco looked back at the drawing room door and tilted his head.

“There’s a young boy and two young girls. The boy is the honorary knight of the Galarc Kingdom named Haruto Amakawa—am I correct?”

“Y-Yes... How did you know that?”

“What is their purpose here? Did you hear anything about their plans?” Reiss asked with a sly grin.

“They wish to send a message to the Galarc Kingdom through our transmission artifact. I will be arranging an inn for them to stay at while they wait for a response, but it seems they plan on leaving this city tomorrow...” Marco took the message paper out of his pocket and held it up.

“I see. What was the message?”

“It’s a report for the King of Galarc. It says he’s secured two important figures and will be bringing them to the castle soon. I believe he means the two girls with him, but... Is there something wrong with that?” Marco asked, suspecting the implication behind Reiss’s prying.

“This is highly confidential, but...”

Marco waved away the soldiers nearby. “You lot can leave.”

Reiss made sure that there was no one left in the hallway. “For now, do not send that message to Galarc. But tell them that you have done so,” he ordered him.

Marco was taken aback for a moment, but then chuckled awkwardly. “You must be joking. If they find out I did such a thing, the Galarc Kingdom might retaliate against us, right?” he asked.

“It’s not a joke. I have no time to explain, either,” Reiss said in a completely serious tone. He then grabbed Marco’s head with his right hand.

“Wh-What?! The disrespect...!” Marco struggled for Reiss to release him, but Reiss’s right hand was like a vise around his head. A dim glow of light shone from Reiss’s palm.

“Ugh...” Marco’s body jolted, then collapsed towards the floor.

“Whoa, there... I see he’s as heavy as he appears.” Reiss gently caught Marco’s bulky body, lending him his shoulder to lean on. He then snatched the paper from Marco’s hand and started down the hallway.

“Is there anyone there?” he called. He turned the corner and went down the hallway.

“Yes...? Huh? Governor?”

A patrolling soldier spotted the two of them and rushed over. “You’re...a guest, right?” the soldier asked Reiss dubiously.

“Yes. My name is Jean Bernard, and I’m a noble of the royal court. I was discussing important matters with Lord Tonteri when he suddenly collapsed—it seems he’s been lacking sleep. Where can I find his bedroom?” Reiss explained the situation to the soldier in an exasperated tone.

“Huh...” The soldier cocked his head, wondering if that was even possible.

“Zzz... Zzz...” Marco snored in his sleep.

“Ha ha... I see. What a terrible snorer,” the soldier snickered inappropriately, before covering his mouth with a gasp. “Oh, please pretend you didn’t hear that.”

“Of course. I was just thinking the same,” Reiss agreed with a chuckle.

“Heh. Right, so the governor’s room is right over there. Let me assist you.” The soldier nearly snickered again, but quickly moved to support Marco on the other side of Reiss. They arrived at Marco’s bedroom in less than a minute and laid him down on the bed.

“Good work. With Lord Tonteri like this, I shall go to the deputy governor and explain the situation. You should head to the drawing room and inform Lord Tonteri’s guests that some urgent business has come up, then show them to an inn. Oh, and tell them that their message has been sent,” Reiss said.

“Understood, sir. Please come this way,” the soldier said respectfully, then began to show Reiss the way.

After that, Reiss went to find the deputy governor of the fort and explained the necessary facts. After carefully laying the groundwork to prevent problems from occurring later, he left the fort. Once he was out of the fortress city, he relocated to the nearby forest.

“Instans Motus.” Taking a teleport crystal out of his breast pocket, he vanished instantly. His destination was still within the Rubia Kingdom—a room of Jean Bernard’s house in the capital. It was essentially a vacant home with no one managing the premises.

“Now, it’s time to win over the hero and Princess Sylvie with Princess Estelle as the reward. I’ll also need to bring Arein and the others along. Time to get things done.”

Reiss left his estate and headed for the castle.

◇　◇　◇

Thus, Reiss visited the Rubia Castle. His position as Jean Bernard was fabricated, but it had its uses within the castle as well. Most people didn’t know of his circumstances and respected him as a noble.

“Your Highness, Reiss has arrived. He’s waiting in the drawing room...”

Reiss had gone through the castle gate to meet with Sylvie. On behalf of her personal knights, Elena went to the room Sylvie had shut herself in to report the situation.

“I’ll head there immediately.”

Sylvie had been seated on the sofa gazing out of the window somberly, but when she heard Elena’s words, she stood up and sighed heavily. It took her a few minutes to relocate.

“Sorry to keep you waiting,” Sylvie entered the drawing room and addressed Reiss flatly.

“Not at all. Thank you for arriving so promptly,” Reiss said, standing up from his chair and replying with a friendly smile.

“Are you here for Renji?” Sylvie cut to the chase to ask whether he was here for his subordinate. She made her way to the seat across from Reiss and sat down. At that, Reiss also sat back down.

“That’s part of it, but I was thinking our relationship could move on to the next stage as well,” Reiss said with a grin.

Sylvie immediately frowned. “The next stage of our relationship...?”

“The current state of the Rubia Kingdom is extremely unstable, don’t you think?”

“Whose fault do you think that is?” Sylvie said coldly.

“It’s because the Rubia Kingdom is a minor nation, of course,” Reiss stated without fear.

“...” Sylvie glared at Reiss in seething anger. She could normally endure things with just a furrowed brow, but her aura was more hostile than usual today.

“With the king in such bad health, you’re handling half of this kingdom’s duties right now. I’m sure you’re more than just a little overworked,” Reiss said with a cool face, as though he was reciting his words.

“I’m in an irritable mood right now. I have no intention of entertaining your disdainful, long-winded speeches. Get to the point.”

“In that case, I shall ask frankly: are you siding with the Galarc Kingdom, or are you swapping loyalties to the Proxia Empire? I would appreciate a straight answer,” Reiss said boldly.

“I’m afraid I can’t make that decision by myself,” Sylvie answered.

“And I’m saying it’s about time you stopped making excuses. Like I said already, it’s time we moved to the next stage of our relationship.” Reiss wouldn’t allow Sylvie to brush off his question.

“In that case, stop putting on that act. Like I said already, get to the point.” Sylvie stared directly back at Reiss.

“I wasn’t putting on an act, but... Ah, I suppose this must be a bad habit of mine. Allow me to rephrase my question, then. Does the Rubia Kingdom have any intention of changing sides from Galarc to Proxia?”

“It depends on the conditions.”

“Well, that’s a welcome change from your attitude in the beginning. We haven’t known each other for that long, but I guess all our interactions have added up to something.” Reiss smiled pleasantly.

In contrast, Sylvie sneered. “Ha.”

“I suppose your change of heart is due to the hero’s defeat the other day.”

“I haven’t changed at all. I still hate you as much as ever. The ways of the Empire too,” Sylvie said, distinctly denying Reiss’s observation.

“I find that resolute disposition of yours to be extremely favorable. Your lack of a scheming side makes you very easy to deal with.”

“That’s because I hate people like you, who have nothing but a scheming side.”

“I hear that a lot.”

“Not that it matters now. Get back to the point,” Sylvie sighed.

“Straightforward is what you want, yes? Then if I may ask, what kind of conditions would make you swap sides from Galarc to Proxia?”

“There are several... But first, we do not want to form an alliance with a country we cannot understand. What merit does the Proxia side gain by having a minor nation like Rubia as an ally? Why are you so concerned about our kingdom?” She wouldn’t allow him to lie his way out of this, and she stared at him to emphasize that.

“Hmm... Then let’s have a bit of a heart-to-heart, shall we? The answer is extremely simple, though—the reason why Rubia caught my eye was because you started to form a favorable friendship with the hero, Renji,” Reiss replied smoothly.

“Wh-What...?” The unexpected answer left Sylvie dumbfounded.

“The Proxia Empire wanted a hero, you see, but unfortunately there weren’t any that were summoned within the country’s borders. So I kept an eye on all the heroes summoned in the nearby countries, and that was when I discovered him.” Reiss continued his explanation with no regard for Sylvie’s state of shock.

“I believe I found him shortly before meeting you, I think? But it was evident that Renji had a tricky personality to deal with. The fact that he was working as an adventurer meant he probably had no intention of allying with your kingdom, but just as I was trying to work out a solution, I learned that he had met you and developed a friendship. And so I thought I could use that,” Reiss concluded.

“Disgusting. You’re revolting,” Sylvie cut in.

“Oh, was I a little too direct? I thought you wanted to understand my intentions.”

“It’s fine... But I still don’t get it. What did you think you could use?”

“Of course, I thought I could use hostages.”

“You mean Estelle?”

“And you as well. People can function as hostages even without being abducted. In addition to Estelle, you’ve also become an irreplaceable existence to the hero Renji, you realize? Enough for him to fight for your sake,” Reiss said knowingly.

“Did you predict this situation from the moment you kidnapped Estelle...?” In other words, had he lured Renji into witnessing the hostage situation, then made him lose to Lucius in order to gain a subordinate?

“Yes. Thanks to that, as long as the Rubia Kingdom joins sides with Proxia, we’ll be able to suppress the risk of the hero rebelling. Wouldn’t you agree?” Reiss said smoothly, as though it was obvious that was the reasoning behind the Proxia Empire’s actions.

Sylvie spat out her feelings bitterly. “Honestly, you’re revolting...”

Apparently that was praise to Reiss, who thanked her with a smile. “I’m honored to receive such praise.”

“...” Sylvie frowned, unable to speak further.

“Have I fulfilled your condition of understanding my intentions?” Reiss asked.

Sylvie nodded with a furrowed brow. “I suppose you could say that...”

“In that case, allow me to offer some attractive benefits in anticipation of the Rubia Kingdom’s cooperation,” Reiss said, changing the topic. “First, if the Rubia Kingdom ever faces conflict with an enemy hereafter, the Proxia Empire will dispatch its Winged Knights to assist in dispatching the enemy forces. We’ll also send over enough demi-dragons to form a small squadron for your army. On top of this, we’ll provide a large amount of funds and resources to assist in the technological development of the kingdom,” he listed.

Sylvie gulped in spite of herself. “That’s an unbelievable offer...”

It was practically unheard of for a major nation to offer a minor nation such favorable conditions. The Galarc Kingdom certainly hadn’t done this much for Rubia.

“I can offer more benefits than that too. Such as returning the person you personally want the most, for example,” Reiss said suggestively.

Sylvie gasped. “You’ll hand Estelle back to us...?”

“Indeed. If you cooperate in resolving a problem I’m dealing with right now, I can return her as early as tomorrow—even without your answer on your kingdom’s official stance.” Reiss grinned eerily.

“...” Sylvie’s face stiffened—she was containing herself from reflexively agreeing with his conditions.

“How about it? The problem I’m dealing with is rather urgent, you see. Even if I receive the hero’s assistance, I still need to relocate to where my other subordinates are waiting. If I cannot receive an answer from you tonight, I’m afraid Princess Estelle’s return will have to be delayed to another day...” Reiss said, indirectly pressing Sylvie for an answer.

“I cannot make a decision without hearing the details. Tell me more,” Sylvie said with a serious expression.

Reiss chuckled, then began to explain the circumstances. “Why, it’s nothing that can’t be solved as long as the Rubia Kingdom allies with Proxia. You see, there’s a certain knight of the Galarc Kingdom staying within Rubian territory right now...”

◇　◇　◇

That night, someone from the fort arranged an inn for Rio, Christina, and Flora to stay in. They were to check for a reply from Galarc in the morning, but if they left it until too late it’d be noontime, so they set off for the fort a little earlier. The inn they stayed at was the best one in the city, and they arrived at the fort in no time at all.

“Did you sleep well last night?” Rio asked Christina and Flora during the short walk.

“It wasn’t as nice as the bed in your house, but I slept soundly,” said Christina.

“Me too. I’ve grown used to taking baths these past few days, so the ones here felt unsatisfactory,” Flora answered with a giggle.

“I feel the same about the baths. Considering how we need to return to Rodania, you might be getting too used to them. There are no facilities like that in Rodania, after all,” Christina said with a wry smile.

Just then, the gate of the fort came into view. They crossed the bridge before the gate to find the same gatekeeper as yesterday standing there.

“Go on through.” He took a look at their faces and allowed them through without a fuss.

We just came yesterday, so it isn’t strange that he remembers our faces, but...wasn’t his expression a little stiff? Did he work through the night?

Rio noticed the guard’s face was oddly tense as he passed him. However, he didn’t pay it any further mind and led the way through the gate. There was an open courtyard past the gate where the sun shone brightly. There was no sign of anyone else in the courtyard, but when they progressed farther forward into the fort, they found three swordsmen dressed in coats. Furthermore, the fortress walls and watchtowers were lined with a crowd of soldiers. Among them was Marco, the governor who had welcomed them yesterday. He looked down on them with a conflicted expression.

What?

It was at this point that Rio raised his guard; he released his magic essence into the air and melded it into the atmosphere. He then activated his spirit arts to search within a radius of over ten meters.

Then, the door of the gate slammed down behind them.

“Huh?”

“Eek!”

Christina’s and Flora’s shaken voices could be heard from behind Rio.

There are soldiers outside the gate, but none behind us. They closed the gate, so they won’t be coming in. The enemy is only to the front and along the walls...

Rio had gathered his thoughts that far, when the soldiers on the fort walls drew back their bows and fired their arrows at once.

“Stay behind me,” Rio said to the two behind him. An uncountable volley of arrows came flying.

“Huh?!”

Rio drew his sword and created a sphere of wind around Christina and Flora, protecting them. The rain of arrows had their trajectory altered by the wind wall and stabbed into the ground. The soldiers gazed at the scene in dumbfounded silence.

“Bastard! How dare ya kill the captain!”

The largest of the three coat-clad swordsmen standing ten meters before Rio removed his hood and yelled at him.

He was the one with Reiss when we were moving from Cleia to Rodania...

Arein, Lucci, Ven. Lucius’s three subordinates. The three of them drew their swords and chanted a spell together.

“Augendae Corporis!”

They use their enchanted swords together with their physical ability enhancements to become twice as strong, if I recall correctly.

Rio immediately recalled the way they fought and poured magic essence into his sword. At the same time, Arein and the others split up and closed in on Rio from three directions. Rio braced his sword and swung it not at the three of them, but towards the sky overhead. A tremendous explosion thundered, sending a fierce gale of cold air through the area.

“Wha?!”

Rio’s attack had been directed at a boy holding a halberd. He had been hidden on top of the gate in order to ambush them. His eyes were widened at how easily his surprise attack had been defended against. Despite the fact he swung his halberd with the momentum of his fall from above, the boy lost in strength and was pushed back.

“Guh!”

He was thrown slightly off balance and landed back on top of the gate. It was then that Rio was able to see his opponent’s face—it was Kikuchi Renji, the Japanese boy summoned as a hero.

“The fifth hero...?” Rio murmured to himself as he spotted his clearly Japanese appearance and the divine-looking halberd in his hand.

Renji looked down at Rio with a sharp glare.

“Hey, rookie! That was pathetic!” Lucci yelled angrily at Renji.

“Hmph...” Renji snorted unhappily and lifted his halberd.

That distortion of mana and the cold wind from the first attack... He can control air.

Rio poured essence into his sword once more.

“Photon Projectilis!”

Arein and the men used the photon bullet spell to attack. With his attention on Renji, Rio came under concentrated fire. However, he concentrated the wind wall around him towards the front and blocked it.

At the same time, countless spears of ice fell from above—those came from Renji. Rio swung his sword and released a wind-clad strike to repel the spears.

“Tch.” Renji backed away in a hurry, hiding from the projectiles.

Neither the boy above, the three men in front, nor the soldiers on the wall are getting close. How troublesome. They’re focused only on provoking me. For a group that was waiting in ambush, they’re surprisingly cautious.

Rio analyzed the enemy’s tactics. Because he had to protect Christina and Flora, he was in a similar situation to when he fought Lucius. He’d be able to crush them individually if he could move freely, but with people to protect, his movement was limited. However, they weren’t as threatening as Lucius, who had been able to move through space.

“Are you two okay?” Rio asked the two behind him.

“Yes,” Christina answered. She held Flora in her arms to protect her.

“The three men in front of me are Lucius’s subordinates, and the one on top of the gate is probably the fifth hero. They also seem to have the Rubian soldiers of the fort on their side... I don’t understand what’s going on,” Rio said to them.

“Sir Amakawa, is there anything we can do?”

“Can the two of you use barrier magic? And preferably keep it up for thirty seconds?”

Christina and Flora exchanged a look before nodding. “Yes...”

“At my signal, stand back-to-back inside the gate and use that magic. I’ll reduce the enemy’s forces in thirty seconds.”

If the enemy wasn’t going to make the first move, then he would.

Christina gulped. “I understand. We’re ready whenever,” she replied.

“Then... Go!” Rio said loudly.

“Let’s do this, Flora!”

“Right!”

Christina and Flora stood back-to-back inside the gate. “Magicae Murum!” they chanted together. A magic circle immediately appeared before the two girls, creating a giant wall of light in front of them.

Rio felt the wave of magic essence behind him and sent a burst of wind at the three men coming to attack him.

“Ngh...”

The three of them leaped high and avoided the attack, but Rio kicked off the ground and approached Lucci, who was directly before him.

“Ha! This is for the captain!” Lucci grinned fiercely, swinging his sword at Rio’s approach. Their swords clashed with each other, but Rio won in strength and knocked Lucci’s sword away, sending him crashing into the wall.

“Urgh, damn it...” Lucci’s face twisted in vexation. At this point, Rio’s attention was turned to Ven, who was still in the air from his leap and couldn’t move. He sent essence into his sword and pointed the tip at him.

“Hah...!” He fired a blast of wind to blow Ven back to the wall. There didn’t seem to be any formidable opponents amongst the fort soldiers, leaving only Arein and Renji. At this point, only ten seconds had passed.

“Rookie! Get the princesses!” Arein landed on the ground and yelled at Renji on top of the gate.

“Tch...” Renji hesitated for a moment, then leapt down from the gate. He poured essence into the halberd in his hand to attack the magic barrier that Christina had up.

Christina stiffened. “Eek...!”

“What?!”

However, the tip of the halberd Renji swung down was frozen just inches before grazing the wall. Rio had squeezed himself between them and caught the halberd with his sword.

Lifting his blade vertically upwards, he deflected the halberd away. With a quick step backwards, Renji tried to gain distance from Rio, but Rio tackled Renji’s undefended torso with his back.

“Guh...!” The force was diminished thanks to the backstep, but Renji was still blown away dramatically.

“Wh-What’s with this guy...?” Renji picked himself up after rolling across the ground and questioned Arein beside him.

Arein glared at Rio in detestation. “Hah! He’s the one who killed the man you lost to.”

“What...?” Renji’s eyes shook.

“You can disperse the barrier for now. Stay hidden underneath the gate, but be careful of the enemies on the other side.”

Rio watched Renji and Arein as he stood before the gate, blocking their way to the princesses he was speaking to. He sent essence into his sword in order to be able to react at a moment’s notice.

“Okay.” As soon as they replied, Christina and Flora dispersed the magic barrier they had set up.

“It’s infuriating, but he’s got a monstrous amount of strength. Completely different from you. You couldn’t even protect Princess Sylvie and Princess Estelle, huh?” Arein said to Renji with a mocking sneer.

Renji glared back at him. “Shut up...” He then turned to glare at Rio.

I understand the mercenaries’ hostility, but why does the hero have so much aggression towards me? Maybe I should dig a little deeper, Rio wondered to himself, then made a decision.

“Are you the hero of the Rubia Kingdom?” he asked, looking at Renji.

“Hmph.” Renji merely huffed sullenly.

“I failed to inform you yesterday, but the two people with me are the Beltrum Kingdom’s Princess Christina and Princess Flora. Am I correct in assuming this attack is made with that knowledge?” Rio asked the governor hiding in a corner of the fortress wall. Arein had looked at the girls and called them princesses during the battle, so he believed the soldiers of the fort were cooperating with Arein while knowing the truth.

“Wha...” Marco’s face twisted in fear as he tried to open his mouth. But before he could, countless attack spells started raining down on the courtyard of the fort.

“Ngh...” Rio swung his sword and released a gust of wind to slice apart the attack spells and cancel them out. His view cleared to reveal female knights riding on griffins.

Hmm? Where have I seen that woman before?

There was one woman among them dressed in particularly ornate armor who looked familiar to him. Of course she would—he had met her at the banquet in the Galarc Kingdom. It was First Princess Sylvie.

“Impossible... You blocked that?” Sylvie looked down at Rio with widened eyes, her expression shocked.

“S-Sir Amakawa. The flag that the griffin squad is holding belongs to Rubia’s royal family! And the person over there is Princess Sylvie!” Christina yelled from below the gate, pointing at the griffins.

Which means the Rubia Kingdom is part of this whole situation after all. If the three mercenaries are here, then the Proxia Empire is involved too? Rio thought immediately.

“All units, attack from above! Kill that man no matter what!” Sylvie pointed her sword at Rio and gave the surrounding griffin squad the order to attack, then immediately fired a ray of essence light from her sword. The other female knights riding the griffins also used spells to bombard Rio with attacks.

“Thank you for waiting. Please come in, Lady Satsuki. Everyone, please be seated. The servants may leave.” Francois invited Satsuki into the room and sat down on a sofa himself.

Are we about to discuss something confidential? Liselotte wondered.

“Hey, Liselotte. It’s been a while... Since the dinner at your place, I think?” Satsuki said to her cheerfully.

“Yes. Long time no see, Miss Satsuki.” Liselotte smiled with a sigh of relief.

“Honestly, I wanted to attend that dinner so much. Come on, now. Lady Satsuki. Sit over here.” Charlotte pouted cutely and urged Satsuki into the head seat. They passed the servants on their way into the room and sat down. Duke Cretia and his wife selected seats diagonal to them and seated themselves.

“Your Majesty. Please accept my sincere apologies for rejecting the hero’s marriage proposal,” Liselotte said to King Francois, bowing where she stood.

“Don’t worry about it. You’ve achieved enough to earn your freedom in marriage. That is something I have acknowledged myself, and I expected you to decline this offer from the beginning. However, the current state of the Restoration complicated things. I had to give the other side a chance to meet you to avoid souring relations. I’m sure that made it more difficult for you to decline. My apologies for that,” Francois said, sighing tiredly.

“No, I am most grateful for your consideration, Your Majesty.”

It was at this moment that Liselotte finally relaxed. She had sensed that things had been arranged to make it harder for her to refuse when she was devoid of the chance to confirm Francois and her parents’ thoughts on the matter. She figured Duke Huguenot had arranged that with Francois, but his words just now confirmed her thoughts. And the fact he had revealed this to her meant that there was no issue in her rejecting the proposal.

“It seems like our worries were for naught, Lady Satsuki,” Charlotte giggled.

“So it seems,” Satsuki replied with a faint pout.

“The two of you were worried...?” Liselotte cocked her head.

“Isn’t it your belief that marriage should only be done out of love? If you agreed so easily to an arranged marriage, you’d be throwing away that belief. Lady Satsuki and I were worried you were being forced into the engagement.”

“I-I see... I appreciate that,” Liselotte said with a faint blush.

“But rest assured, if that man ever tries to force you into an engagement, I’ll stop him with my own authority as a hero,” Satsuki said firmly.

“Aha ha. I’m glad your fears were unfounded, then.” Liselotte sweated nervously at the thought of the trouble that would have created. Francois must have felt uneasy at that as well.

“But you can’t remain without a marriage partner at your age either, Liselotte—that’s asking for trouble to come to you, you know?” Charlotte pointed out with a heavy sigh.

“I’m sure it’s a challenge to find a boy worthy of someone like Liselotte,” Satsuki said with a giggle.

“Th-That’s not true...” Liselotte stuttered. Her parents watched that rare sight with curious looks. They were impressed that the princess and hero could make their daughter react in a way fitting for her age for once.

“Oh, speaking of gentlemen worthy of Liselotte, I believe I know of someone...” Charlotte put on a mischievous face.

“Th-This is urgent! I have an urgent report to make! Excuse the intrusion!” Fierce banging sounded from the door moments before it burst open to reveal a breathless knight.

“How dare you enter without waiting for a response?! What is it? This better be important!” Francois warned with a furrowed brow.

“Honorary Knight Sir Amakawa has arrived! H-He requests an immediate audience with Your Majesty!” The knight was so heavily flustered, he made his report without a second thought for Francois’ anger.

“Haruto, you say? In that case, you can bring him here. What is the reason for the urgency?”

“Th-That’s because he’s accompanied by...” The knight wheezed, out of breath from running the whole way here.

“What is it? Calm down and speak. What about his companions?” Francois asked unhappily.

“He’s accompanied by Beltrum’s First Princess Christina and Second Princess Flora!”

The two missing princesses were alive.

“What...?” At that moment, even Francois was as dumbfounded as everyone else present.

Interlude: Duke Huguenot’s Melancholy

Four days had passed since Rio was ambushed in Rubia, and ten days had passed since Christina and Flora first disappeared.

Liselotte had just boarded an enchanted ship with Roanna, who came to her as a messenger. They departed from Amande to meet Hiroaki about the arranged marriage.

Meanwhile, in the Galarc Castle, Duke Huguenot was alone in his room and sitting on the sofa. He took a deep breath to calm himself.

Roanna contacted me earlier. Liselotte will arrive in Galarc in a few hours. Finally. Finally, it will be time...

He was nervous—a rare look for him. And it was all because the fate of the Restoration, and of Duke Huguenot himself, depended on the results of this discussion.

I’ve somehow managed to set up a meeting to at least discuss the marriage, but...

In all honesty, the situation wasn’t looking good.

I’ve gotten King Francois’ help, but that was only for setting up the meeting. He emphasized that he wouldn’t force Liselotte into a marriage.

The Restoration was a vital piece of protection for the Galarc Kingdom—this was why Francois had agreed to the marriage between the third princess and Hiroaki; in effect, he’d forced his own daughter into marriage.

However, even if it was for the Restoration, he wouldn’t force his vassal’s daughter into a marriage. This meant that Liselotte Cretia held more importance to Francois than his own daughter.

Of course he would. He could use a royal decree on her, but doing so would antagonize Liselotte. Losing Liselotte would mean losing the Ricca Guild—which could end up impacting Galarc’s economy.

Furthermore, he had heard rumors that Liselotte was good friends with the hero, Satsuki. It was only natural for Francois to tread carefully.

We should be grateful he even helped set up this meeting out of consideration of the Restoration and respect for our hero. He even promised not to mention to Liselotte that he didn’t mind if she turned down the marriage. Which only leaves Sir Hiroaki’s proposal and Liselotte’s reply... But...

It’d be simple if Francois just ordered Liselotte to marry, but that wouldn’t happen. A meeting was the second best option, but it left Duke Huguenot feeling uneasy.

Things will also depend on how much value Liselotte placed on Sir Hiroaki’s position as a hero. But really, our chances are slim.

Duke Huguenot was aware of the fact that Hiroaki was infatuated with Liselotte, which was why he had observed their previous interactions to see if things could go well between them.

Liselotte is a noblewoman, but she’s also a merchant when there are profits to be gained. She sought her own freedom in marriage because she understands that her greatest asset is herself. It would be one thing if the organization was in its best condition with Princess Christina and Princess Flora present, but even I can’t see anything that would appeal to her in the current state of the Restoration.

Duke Huguenot’s analysis was generally correct—the only point he had missed was the possibility that Liselotte wanted to marry as a normal girl. But that was an unavoidable error under the current situation. Presently, the Restoration was being backed by the Galarc Kingdom. In accordance with this, they were receiving funds and resources from the Ricca Guild, so Liselotte was well versed in the internal affairs of the organization. She should’ve had a clear understanding of the negative effects of Christina and Flora’s disappearance—and of the fact that Hiroaki’s betrothal with Rosalie wouldn’t be enough to completely erase those effects.

I must plan for when the marriage discussion fails...

Duke Huguenot pondered over the conditions Hiroaki presented for his betrothal to Rosalie—in other words, to receive Liselotte as his third wife.

There’s no telling what Sir Hiroaki’s mood will be until after he’s actually rejected... Who knows which way the dice will fall.

Just imagining it was enough to give him a headache.

However, even if Liselotte rejects the proposal, I must make sure Sir Hiroaki marries Rosalie no matter what.

If he failed to do that, the Restoration would be over. What steps could he take to prevent that? Duke Huguenot struggled against the pressure weighing on him as he waited for Liselotte’s arrival.